Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of Geographic Images circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: New York City Views - Manhattan, 50413
  - Subseries IB: MANHATTAN - FLAT MATERIALS - PRINTS, 190608
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Views, 216809
      - Harbor Views- 1800 - 1839, 190628 (Folder FF20)
        View of the Bay and Harbour of New York, from the Battery, Smith after Burton, pub. in New York Mirror, 1830
        Entry to the Bay of New-York, Salathe after Ch. Bodmar, 1839
        New-York taken from Fort Columbus, Governor's Island 1816, Hayward's Lithography for Valentine's Manual ,1860.
      - Harbor Views- 1840 - 1849, 190629 (Folder FF21)
      - Harbor Views- Views by Havell, 1844. Panoramic View of New York taken from the North River; Panoramic View of New York taken from the East River. Robert Havell, 190630 (Folder FF22)
        Panoramic View of New York taken from the North River, 1844, Robert Havell
        Panoramic View of New York taken from the East River, 1844, Robert Havell.
      - Harbor Views- 1846-1848, 190631 (Folder FF23)
        New York taken from the Northwest Angle of Fort Columbus, Governor's Island, 1846, Henry Papprill, after Catherwood
        New York and Environs from Williamsburgh, 1848, E.W. Foreman and E. Brown Jr.
      - Harbor Views- Views by Nathaniel Currier, 1849, 216628 (Folder FF24)
        City of New York, from Jersey City, Nathaniel Currier, lithographer, 1849
        New York Bay from the Telegraph Station, Nathaniel Currier, lithographer, 1849
        View of New York from Brooklyn Heights, Nathaniel Currier, lithographer, 1849
        View of New York from Weehawken-North River, Nathaniel Currier, lithographer, 1849.
      - Harbor Views- 1850 - 1859, 190633 (Folder FF25)
        New-York, Vue Prise du Fort de William-Castle, Lebreton, lithographer, printed in Paris [1850-59]
        Vue de New-York, Prise de L'Ile Ellis, Lebreton, lithographer, printed in Paris [1850-59].
      - Harbor Views- 1850-1851, 190634 (Folder FF26)
        View of New York and its Environs taken from the Heights of West Hoboken, Jacottet and Bayot, lithographers, [1850]
        View of New York from the East River, Robert Hinshel, engraver (attributed), 1851
        Souvenir of New York, C. Gildemeister, lithographer after J. Bornet, 1851
        View of New York from the North River.
      - Harbor Views- Floating Grain Elevators, 190635 (Folder FF27)
      - Harbor Views- 1860 - 1899, 190636 (Folder FF28)
        New York Bay, from Bay Ridge, L.I., Currier & Ives, 1860
        The Harbour of New York from the Brooklyn Bridge Tower Looking South-west, Currier & Ives.
      - Harbor Views- 1900 and later, 190637 (Folder FF29)
      - Winter Views, 190638 (Folder FF30)
        Sleighing in New York, Benecke, lithographer
        Life in New York! (Sleighing in Winter), J. Dorival, publisher.
      - Fictitious Views, French/German, 190639 (Folder FF31)
        Nowel Amsterdam en L'Amerique 1672 (Quebec origin)
        [View in 1666]
        [Triumphal Entry of Royal Troops to New York]
        [Debarkment of English troops at New York]
        Related Archival Materials Note
        See also: similar views filed under Boston and Philadelphia
      - Fictitious Views, French/German origin, 217523 (Folder FF32)
        [Destruction of the Royal Statue in New York] (4)
        [Terrible Fire in New York September 19, 1776] (2)
        [The Arrival of Prince William Henry October 16 1781]
        Incendie de New-Yorck, 1835 [Great Fire of 1835]
      - General views/Sets of views, 190641 (Folder FF33)
        "The Picturesque Tourist" 1845
        "The Pocket Annual" 1848
        "Historical New York," Albertypes from the Leonard
        Hassam Bogart Collection, 1939
        "An Album of Contemporary New York" [1950-70]
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Rivers, 216819
      - East River (General), 190642 (Folder FF34)
      - East River (Hell Gate), 190643 (Folder FF35)
      - Harlem River, 190644 (Folder FF36)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Islands, 216820
      - Liberty Island (Bedloe's Island)and Statue of Liberty, 190645 (Folder FF37)
      - Islands, other, 190646 (Folder FF38)
        Governor's Island
        Randall's Island
        Roosevelt Island (Welfare Island/Blackwell's Island)
        Ward's Island
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Bridges, 216822
      - Brooklyn Bridge, 190647 (Folder FF39)
      - High Bridge, 190648 (Folder FF40)
      - Bridges, other, 190649 (Folder FF41)
        Harlem Bridge
        Manhattan Bridge
        Williamsburg Bridge
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Street Views, 216823
      - A - B named streets, 190650 (Folder FF42)
        Albany Street; Baxter Street; Barclay Street; Beekman Street; Bowery
      - Broad Street, 190652 (Folder FF43)
      - Broadway- Battery Place north to Wall Street, 190654 (Folder FF44)
      - Broadway- Wall Street north to Fulton Street, 190655 (Folder FF45)
      - Broadway- Fulton Street north to Worth Street, 190656 (Folder FF46-47)
      - Broadway- looking south from Barclay Street and Park to American Museum, St. Paul's, Astor House, 216808 (Folder FF48)
      - Broadway- View of St. Paul's and the Broadway Stages, 1831, 190657 (Folder FF49)
      - Broadway- Worth Street north to 23rd Street, 190658 (Folder FF50)
      - C - L named streets, 190659 (Folder FF51)
        Canal Street; Cherry Street; Coenties Slip; Dover Street; Edgar Street; Fulton Street; Herald Square; Hester Street; Liberty Street
      - M - P named streets, 190660 (Folder FF52)
        Madison Avenue, Madison Square, Maiden Lane, Murray Street, Park Avenue, Park Place, Park Row, Pine Street, Printing House Square
      - Q - Z named streets, 190661 (Folder FF53)
        South Street, West Street
      - Wall Street, 190662 (Folder FF54-55)
      - Numbered Streets and Avenues, 190664 (Folder FF56)
        42nd Street (Fifth Avenue to Lexington Avenue); W. 80th Street (Columbus Avenue to Amsterdam Avenue); Second Avenue (north from 42nd St.); Fifth Avenue (north and south from 42nd St.)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Neighborhoods, 216824
      - Five Points/Collect Pond, 190665 (Folder FF57)
      - Chinatown,Greenwich Village, Harlem, Manhattanville, 190666 (Folder FF58)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Parks and Gardens, 216825
      - Battery Park, 190667 (Folder FF59-60)
      - Central Park (Genre prints published by Schile), 190669 (Folder FF61)
      - Central Park (Maps, plans, panoramas), 190670 (Folder FF62)
      - Central Park (Buildings, monuments, structures, etc.), 190671 (Folder FF63)
      - Central Park (Activities and events with winter sports), 190672 (Folder FF64)
      - City Hall Park (19th century), 190673 (Folder FF65)
      - City Hall Park (later repros of 19th century prints), 190674 (Folder FF66)
      - Jones Wood, 190675 (Folder FF67)
      - Union Square, 190676 (Folder FF68)
      - Gardens- Elgin Botanic Garden; Palace Garden, 190677 (Folder FF69)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Buildings, 216826
      - Armories- Seventh Regiment (3rd Ave at 6th St.), 190678 (Folder FF70)
      - Baths- Russian Baths, 190679 (Folder FF71)
      - Churches and Synagogues- Protestant Episcopal Churches after G. Stacy photographs; misc. pew plans, 1867; 190680 (Folder FF72)
      - Churches and Synagogues- A- E, 190681 (Folder FF73)
        All Souls Unitarian Church
        Annunciation Episcopal Church (pew plan)
        Bethel Ship John Wesley
        B'nai Jeshurun
        Brick Presbyterian Church (includes pew plan)
        Calvary Episcopal Church
        Christ's Lutheran Church
        Divine Unity, Church of (pew plan)
      - Churches and Synagogues- F - I, 190682 (Folder FF74)
        First Congregational Church
        First Presbyterian Church
        Floating Church of Our Savior
        Holy Communion, Church of the
        Incarnation, Episcopal Church of the (pew plan)
      - Churches and Synagogues- First Methodist Episcopal and First Mariners Methodist Episcopal Church, 190683 (Folder FF75)
      - Churches and Synagogues- Grace Church, 190684 (Folder FF76)
      - Churches and Synagogues- J - R, 190685 (Folder FF77)
        Little Church Around the Corner (Church of the Transfiguration)
        Messiah, Unitarian Church of the (pew plan)
        Middle Dutch Church
        Moravian Church
        New Dutch Church
        North Reformed Dutch Church
        Puritans, Presbyterian Church of the
      - Churches and Synagogues- S - Z, 190686 (Folder FF78)
        St. Alphonsus
        St. Ann's Church for Deaf Mutes
        St. Bernard's
        St. Esprit, Eglise Francoise du
        St. George's Episcopal Church
        St. Johannes
        St. John's Episcopal Chapel
        St. John the Divine, Episcopal Cathedral Church of
        St. Michael's
        St. Thomas Episcopal Church
        South Dutch Church
      - Churches and Synagogues- St. Mark's Episcopal in the Bouwerie, 190687 (Folder FF79)
      - Churches and Synagogues- St. Patrick's Roman Catholic Cathedral, 190688 (Folder FF80)
      - Churches and Synagogues- St. Paul's Episcopal Chapel, 190689 (Folder FF81)
      - Churches and Synagogues- Trinity Church, 190690 (Folder FF82)
        includes "Birdseye View of Trinity Church," 1847, by John Forsyth; and a drawing of old Trinity Church by A.J. Davis.
      - Clubs and Societies- Masonic Hall and Union League Club, 190692 (Folder FF83)
      - Clubs and Societies- Tammany Hall, 190693 (Folder FF84)
      - Financial and Commercial- Banks, 190694 (Folder FF85)
      - Financial and Commercial- Merchant's Exchange, 190696 (Folder FF86)
      - Financial and Commercial- Produce Exchange and Stock Exchange, 190695 (Folder FF87)
      - Financial and Commercial- Insurance, 190697 (Folder FF88)
        Equitable Life Building
        International Insurance Company Building
        Metropolitan Life Building
      - Financial and Commercial- Markets, 190698 (Folder FF89)
        Fulton Fish Market
        Washington Market
      - Financial and Commercial- Offices, 190699 (Folder FF90)
        130 Broadway
        Adams Building, 61 Broadway
        American Express Depot and Offices
        AT&T World Headquarters
        Flatiron Building
        Rockefeller Center
      - Financial and Commercial- Stores and Shops, 190700 (Folder FF91)
        Atlantic Dynamite Company
        Bagoe's first drugstore
        Bourne's Stationers
        Devlin & Co., Clothiers & Gentlemen's Furnishings
        Allen Dodworth, music teacher
        Doremus, Suydams & Nixon Dry Goods
        M. & S.S. Howell, dealers in Gun Powder
        Phelps & Peck's (ruins of)
        T.J. Wood's Tool Store
        John W. Quincy, Cut Nails & Iron
      - Financial and Commercial- Stores and Shops (large), 216872 (Folder 91.5)
        A. T. Stewart's Dept. Store
        Knox the Hatter
        Siegel-Cooper Dept. Store
      - Government Buildings- Castle Garden Immigration Station, 190701 (Folder FF92)
      - Government Buildings- City Hall, Wall Street, 190702 (Folder FF93)
      - Government Buildings- City Hall (Holland/Robinson view), 190703 (Folder FF94)
      - Government Buildings- City Hall, in City Hall Park, 190704 (Folder FF95)
      - Government Buildings- Custom House, Wall Street and Bowling Green, 190705 (Folder FF96)
      - Government Buildings- Fire Departments and Fire Houses, 190706 (Folder FF97)
      - Government Buildings- Government House, Bowling Green, 190707 (Folder FF98)
      - Government Buildings- Post Offices, 190708 (Folder FF99)
      - Government Buildings- Prisons, 190709 (Folder FF100)
      - Government Buildings- other, 190710 (Folder FF101)
        City Hall, Dutch (Stadt Huys), Pearl Street
        Municipal Building
        Hall of Records, City Hall Park
      - Hotels- A - E, 190711 (Folder FF102)
        Albion Hotel
        American Hotel
        Hotel Astor
        Athenaeum Hotel
        Hotel Croton
      - Hotels- City Hotel, 190712 (Folder FF103)
      - Hotels- F- M, 190713 (Folder FF104)
        Fifth Avenue Hotel
        Gramercy Park Hotel
        Grand Union Hotel
        Hurlgate Ferry House
        Madison Cottage
        Metropolitan Hotel
      - Hotels- N - Z, 190714 (Folder FF105)
        New York Hotel
        Park Hotel
        Savoy Plaza and Netherland
        St. Nicholas Hotel
        Hotel St. Stephen
        Sturtevant House
        Union Place Hotel
        United States Hotel
        Washington Hotel
      - Hotels- Pacific Hotel, 190715 (Folder FF106)
      - Institutions- Homes and Asylums, 190716 (Folder FF107)
        Five Points House of Industry
        Home for the Friendless
        Lunatic Asylum
        New York Institution for the Deaf and Dumb
        Poor House
      - Institutions- Hospitals, 217224 (Folder FF108)
        Emigrant Hospital, Ward's Island
        Mount Sinai Hospital
        New York Hospital
        Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
        St. Luke's Hospital
        St. Vincent's Hospital
        Woman's Hospital
      - Libraries and Museums, 190717 (Folder FF109)
        Barnum's Museum (see also: EVENTS- Fire)
        Leavitt Art Rooms
        New York Public Library (42nd and Fifth)
        New York Society Library
      - Manufacturies and Warehouses- Breweries, 190718 (Folder FF110)
        Old Brewery at Five Points
        Daniel Winken's Brewery
      - Manufacturies and Warehouses- Sugar refineries, 190719 (Folder FF111)
        Dennis Harris' Steam Sugar Refinery
        New York Steam Sugar Refining Company
      - Manufactories and Warehouses- other, 190720 (Folder FF112)
        F. Basham, Models, Plaster and Cement Works
        Christy, Constant & Co. Paper-hanging Manufactory
        Fisher & Bird Marbleworks
        Allan Hay & Co. Soap and Candle Works
        E. Morgan's Steam Soap and Candle Manufactory
        Neptune Iron Works
        Steinway & Son Piano Factory
        R.M. Stivers Carriage Manufactory
        Henry Thayer & Co.
        Tucker, Cooper & Co. Cordage and Bagging Factory
        Abraham Van Ness, Fire Engine Builder
      - Monuments and Statuary- Grant's Tomb, 190722 (Folder FF113A-113B)
      - Monuments and Statuary- other, 190721 (Folder FF114)
        Dewey Arch
        Sailors and Soldiers Monument
        Victory Arch, 1919, Madison Square
        Worth Monument
      - Printing, Publishing and Newspapers, 190723 (Folder FF114)
        Ackerman & Miller's Sign & Banners
        Hoe Printing Press and Printer's Warehouse
        Joseph Laing & Co. Lithographers
        New York Herald Building (pattern for "doll house" version of building, from 1895 Herald insert)
        Sarles & Adey, music publishers
        The Sun (first office at 222 William Street)
        Tribune Building
        Virtue & Yorston, publishers
        Edward Walker & Sons Book Bindery
      - Residences- A - M, 217266 (Folder FF116)
        Astor, John Jacob
        Bayard, William
        Beekman, James, "Mount Pleasant;"
        Grenzebach Mansion
        Lackson
        Lohmann, Charles R.
        Moore, Clement Clarke
      - Residences- N - Z, 217267 (Folder FF117)
        Parish, Daniel
        Robb, J. Hampden
        Schermerhorn, Peter
        Thomas, Samuel, "Mount Washington;"
        Van Nest, Abraham
        Waddell, W.C.H.
      - Residences- unidentified, 217271 (Folder FF118)
      - Restaurants and Taverns, 217272 (Folder FF119)
        Atlantic Garden
        Beekman Bar
        Brown's Coffeehouse
        Fraunces Tavern
        [German Beer Hall]
      - Schools and Colleges- Columbia University, 217273 (Folder FF120)
      - Schools and Colleges- other, 217274 (Folder FF121)
        College of the City of New York (Lexington and 23rd)
        College of Physicians and Surgeons
        Rutgers Female College
        Theological Seminary of the Protestant Episcopal Church
      - Theaters- A-L, 217287 (Folder FF122)
        Aberle's Theater
        American Theatre
        Bowery Theatre
        Burton's Theatre (see: Palmo's Opera House)
        Carnegie Hall
        Fifth Avenue Theatre
        Hippodrome
        Koster & Bial's Concert Hall
      - Theaters- Castle Garden, 217288 (Folder FF123)
      - Theaters- M - Z, 217289 (Folder FF124)
        Madison Square Theatre
        Mann's Broadway Theatre
        National Theatre
        Niblo's Garden
        Palmo's Opera House
        Park Theatre
        Thalia Theatre
        Winter-Garden (German)
      - Transportation Stations, 217291 (Folder FF125)
        Ferry Terminal, People's Line for Albany
        Grand Central Terminal
        Madison Square Garden as a railroad depot
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Transportation, 217296
      - Street Railroads and Buses, 217294 (Folder FF127)
      - Elevated Railroads, 217293 (Folder FF126)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Utilities, 217297
      - Utilities- A - Z, 217299 (Folder FF128)
        Distributing Reservoir, Fifth Avenue and 42nd Street, 1842
        Receiving Reservoir, Seventh Avenue and 86th Street, 1841
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Prints - Events, 217300
      - Celebrations, 217302 (Folder FF129)
        Croton Water Celebration, 1842
        Hudson-Fulton Celebration, 1909
      - Fairs- American Institute Fair, 1846 and 1848, 217303 (Folder FF130)
      - Fairs- Crystal Palace International Exposition, 1853, 217304 (Folder FF131-132)
      - Fires- Great Fire of 1835, 217307 (Folder FF133)
      - Fires- Great Fire of 1845, 217308 (Folder FF134)
      - Fires- Burning of Barnum's Museum, 217309 (Folder FF135)
      - Fires- Other Fires and Disasters, 217310 (Folder FF136)
        Explosion of a Steam Boiler, 1850
        Burning of the American Theatre, 1836
        Burning of the National Theater, 1839
        Burning of the City Hall, 1858
        Ruins of the Phelps and Peck Store, 1832
        New York World Building Fire, 1882
      - Funerals, 217311 (Folder FF137)
        Andrew Jackson funerary parade, 1845
        Daniel O'Connell, 1847
        U.S. Grant funeral procession, 1885
      - Parades and Processions, 217326 (Folder FF138)
        Grand Reception of Kossuth, 1851
        Seventh Regiment Parade, 1856
        Grand Procession of Wide-Awakes, 1860
        Presentation of Colors to the 20th US Colored Infantry, 1864
        Procession in Honor of the Fenian Exiles, 1871
        George Washington's Entry into New York, 1783
        Second Triennnial Parade of the NY Fire Department, [1859]
        Illuminated Parade of the Fire Department passing Harry Howard's residence, 1858
        Torchlight Procession of NY Firemen
      - Parades and Processions (large), 217390 (Folder FF139)
        Whig Procession, 1844
        Entrance of General Paez, 1850
        When Kossuth Rode Up Broadway, [ca. 1851]
        Departure of the Seventh Regiment for the War, 1861 (2 copies)
        Dewey Land Parade, September 1899
      - Political Campaigns and Conventions, 217400 (Folder 140)
        Meeting to ratify the nomination of Greeley & Brown
      - Riots, 217401 (Folder 141)
        Astor Place Opera House, 1849
  - Subseries IC: MANHATTAN - FLAT MATERIALS- PHOTOS, 50556
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Photos - Views, 217531
      - Aerial Views- Lower Manhattan, looking south (including Battery), 19th century; 217534 (Folder FF142)
      - Aerial Views- Lower Manhattan, looking toward Brooklyn Bridge, 19th century; 217535 (Folder FF143-144)
      - Aerial Views- Lower Manhattan, looking north and west, 19th century; 217536 (Folder FF145)
      - Aerial Views- Manhattan above Canal Street, 19th century; 217537 (Folder FF146)
      - Aerial Views- Entire Borough of Manhattan, 20th century; 217538 (Folder FF147)
      - Aerial Views- below Chambers Street, 20th century; 217540 (Folder FF148)
      - Aerial Views- Chambers Street north to 42nd Street, 20th century; 217541 (Box FF149)
        includes a set of Wurts Bros. photos taken from the top of the Metropolitan Life Building ca. 1909.
      - Aerial Views- 42nd Street north to 59th Street, 20th century; 217542 (Folder FF150)
      - Aerial Views- north of 59th Street, 20th century; 217543 (Folder FF151)
      - Harbor Views- taken from the East River, 19th century; 217549 (Folder FF152)
      - Harbor Views- taken from the Hudson River, 19th century; 217551 (Folder FF153)
      - Harbor Views- taken from the East River, 20th century; 217552 (Folder FF154-155)
      - Harbor Views- taken from the Bay, showing southern tip of Manhattan, 20th century; 217553 (Folder FF156-157)
      - Harbor Views- taken from the Hudson River, 20th century; 217554 (Folder FF158-159)
      - Night Views, 217555 (Folder FF160)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Photos - Rivers, 217556
      - East River- general, 217564 (Folder FF161)
      - East River- showing piers, 217565 (Folder FF162)
      - East River- Hell Gate, 217567 (Folder FF163)
      - Harlem River and Spuyten Duyvil Creek, 217568 (Folder FF164)
      - Hudson River, 217575 (Folder FF165)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Photos - Islands, 217579
      - Ellis Island, 217580 (Folder FF166)
      - Governor's Island, 217583 (Folder FF167)
      - Liberty Island (Bedloe's Island), including Statue Of Liberty; North Brother's Island, 217585 (Folder FF168)
      - Randall's Island; Roosevelt Island, 217591 (Folder FF169)
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Photos - Bridges, 217601
      - Brooklyn Bridge- under construction, looking towards Brooklyn, 217602 (Folder FF170)
      - Brooklyn Bridge- under construction, looking towards Manhattan, 217644 (Folder FF171)
      - Brooklyn Bridge- completed, looking toward Brooklyn, 217645 (Folder FF172)
      - Brooklyn Bridge- completed, looking toward Manhattan, 217646 (Folder FF173)
      - Brooklyn Bridge- full span, 217647 (Folder FF174)
      - Brooklyn Bridge- views taken on bridge, 217648 (Folder FF175)
      - Brooklyn Bridge- larger photos, 217649 (Folder FF176)
        includes image of the General Slocum steamboat sailing under bridge.
      - High Bridge, 217650 (Folder FF177)
      - George Washington Bridge, 217651 (Folder FF178)
        includes 1890 photogravure taken by William Henry Jackson.
      - Bridges- other, 217652 (Folder FF179)
        Central Bridge; Harlem Bridge; Third Avenue Bridge; Manhattan Bridge; Queensborough Bridge; Verrazano Bridge.
    - Manhattan - Flat Material - Photos - Street Views, 217653
      - Named Streets, 218484
        - Amsterdam Avenue (Tenth Avenue), 217655 (Folder FF180)
        - Astor Place, 217874 (Folder FF181)
        - Streets- B, 217893 (Folder FF182)
          Barclay Street
          Barrow Street
          Beaver Street
          Bedford Street
          Bowery
        - Beekman Street, 218133 (Folder FF183)
        - Bleecker Street, 218134 (Folder FF184)
        - Broad Street, 218131 (Folder FF185-186)
        - Broadway - Battery Place/Bowling Green north to Morris Street, 218139 (Folder FF187)
        - Broadway - Morris Street north to Wall Street, 218156 (Folder FF188-189)
        - Broadway - Wall Street north to Fulton Street, 218159 (Folder FF190-191)
        - Broadway - Fulton Street north to Chambers Street, 218161 (Folder FF192-194)
        - Broadway - Chambers Street north to Canal Street, 218162 (Folder FF195-197)
        - Broadway - Canal Street north to 4th Street, 218164 (Folder FF198-199)
        - Broadway - 4th Street north to 10th Street, 218168 (Folder FF200)
        - Broadway - 10th Street north to 14th Street, 218169 (Folder FF201-202)
        - Broadway - 17th Street north to 23rd Street, 218170 (Folder FF203-204)
        - Broadway - 23rd Street north to 34th Street, 218172 (Folder FF205-206)
        - Broadway - 34th Street north to 42nd Streeet, 218174 (Folder FF207-208)